A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1924-1939 FA308
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1933
  - Germany, 1933; 1933/717
    - Germany - List of Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 91, Folder 724)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 91, Folder 725)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 91, Folder 726)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 91, Folder 727)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 728)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 729)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 730)
    - Germany - Murrow Committee for Relief of Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 731)
    - Germany - (A-H), 1933 (Box 92, Folder 732)
    - Germany - (I-M), 1933 (Box 92, Folder 733)
    - Germany - (N-S), 1933 (Box 92, Folder 734)
    - Germany - (S-Z), 1933 (Box 92, Folder 735)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1933 (Box 549, Folder 3658)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1933; 1933/717.A
      - Germany, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 736)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1933; 1933/717.D
      - Germany, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 736)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/717.E
      - Germany, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 736)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1933; 1933/717.R
      - Germany, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 736)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1933; 1933/717.S
      - Germany, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 736)
  - Tanganyika, 1933; 1933/723
    - Tanganyika, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 737)
  - Hungary, 1933; 1933/750
    - Hungary, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 737)
    - Hungary - Nursing, 1933; 1933/750.C
      - Hungary, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 737)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/750.E
      - Hungary, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 737)
  - Italy, 1933; 1933/751
    - Italy, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 737)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1933; 1933/751.A
      - Italy, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 737)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1933; 1933/751.S
      - Italy, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 737)
  - Liberia, 1933; 1933/759
    - Liberia, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
  - Norway, 1933; 1933/767
    - Norway, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/767.E
      - Norway, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
  - Portugal, 1933; 1933/773
    - Portugal - Medical Sciences, 1933; 1933/773.A
      - Portugal, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
    - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/773.E
      - Portugal, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
  - Romania, 1933; 1933/783
    - Romania, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
  - USSR, 1933; 1933/785
    - U.S.S.R., 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
    - USSR - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/785.E
      - U.S.S.R., 1933 (Box 93, Folder 738)
  - Latvia, 1933; 1933/786
    - Latvia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/786.E
      - Latvia, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
  - Finland, 1933; 1933/787
    - Finland, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/787.E
      - Finland, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
  - Poland, 1933; 1933/789
    - Poland, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/789.E
      - Poland, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
  - Siberia, 1933; 1933/791
    - Siberia, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
  - Sweden, 1933; 1933/800
    - Sweden, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1933; 1933/800.A
      - Sweden, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/800.E
      - Sweden, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 739)
  - Switzerland, 1933; 1933/803
    - Switzerland - Social Sciences, 1933; 1933/803.S
      - Switzerland, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 740)
  - Turkey, 1933; 1933/805
    - Turkey, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 740)
  - Syria, 1933; 1933/833
    - Syria, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 740)
    - Syria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1933; 1933/833.E
      - Syria, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 740)
- General Correspondence, 1934
  - International, 1934; 1934/100
    - (A-K), 1934 (Box 93, Folder 741)
    - (L-Z), 1934 (Box 93, Folder 742)
    - International - Nursing, 1934; 1934/100.C
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1934 (Box 93, Folder 742)
    - International - Hookworm, 1934; 1934/100.H
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1934 (Box 93, Folder 742)
    - International - Malaria, 1934; 1934/100.I
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1934 (Box 93, Folder 742)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1934; 1934/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1934 (Box 93, Folder 742)
    - International - Tuberculosis, 1934; 1934/100.T
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1934 (Box 93, Folder 742)
  - United States, 1934; 1934/200
    - United States - (A), 1934 (Box 93, Folder 743)
    - United States - (B-Co), 1934 (Box 93, Folder 744)
    - United States - (Co), 1934 (Box 94, Folder 745)
    - United States - Covington, P. W., 1934 (Box 94, Folder 746)
    - United States - Covington, P. W., 1934 (Box 94, Folder 747)
    - United States - (Coy-Ez), 1934 (Box 94, Folder 748)
    - United States - (F-G), 1934 (Box 94, Folder 749)
    - United States - (H-I), 1934 (Box 94, Folder 750)
    - United States - (J-Ma), 1934 (Box 94, Folder 751)
    - United States - (Mc), 1934 (Box 94, Folder 752)
    - United States - (National Recovery Administration), 1934 (Box 95, Folder 753)
    - United States - (Na-P), 1934 (Box 95, Folder 754)
    - United States - (Q-S), 1934 (Box 95, Folder 755)
    - United States - (T-Z), 1934 (Box 95, Folder 756)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1934; 1934/200.A
      - United States, 1934 (Box 95, Folder 757)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1934; 1934/200.D
      - United States, 1934 (Box 95, Folder 757)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/200.E
      - United States, 1934 (Box 95, Folder 757)
      - United States - (M-Z), 1934 (Box 95, Folder 758)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1934; 1934/200.R
      - United States, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 759)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1934; 1934/200.S
      - United States, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 759)
  - Alabama, 1934; 1934/201
    - Alabama, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 760)
    - Alabama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/201.E
      - Alabama, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 760)
    - Alabama - Public Health Education, 1934; 1934/201.L
      - Alabama, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 760)
  - Arizona, 1934; 1934/203
    - Arizona, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 760)
    - Arizona - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/203.E
      - Arizona, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 760)
  - Arkansas, 1934; 1934/204
    - Arkansas, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 761)
    - Arkansas - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/204.E
      - Arkansas, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 761)
  - California, 1934; 1934/205
    - California, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 762)
    - California, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 763)
    - California - Social Sciences, 1934; 1934/205.S
      - California, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 763)
  - Colorado, 1934; 1934/207
    - Colorado, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 763)
    - Colorado - Medical Sciences, 1934; 1934/207.A
      - Colorado, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 763)
  - Connecticut, 1934; 1934/208
    - Connecticut, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 763)
  - Florida, 1934; 1934/211
    - Florida, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 763)
  - Georgia, 1934; 1934/212
    - Georgia, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 764)
  - Hawaii, 1934; 1934/214
    - Hawaii, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 765)
    - Hawaii - Tuberculosis, 1934; 1934/214.T
      - Hawaii, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 765)
  - Idaho, 1934; 1934/215
    - Idaho, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 765)
    - Idaho - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/215.E
      - Idaho, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 765)
    - Idaho - Public Health Education, 1934; 1934/215.L
      - Idaho, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 765)
  - Illinois, 1934; 1934/216
    - Illinois, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 766)
    - Illinois - Social Sciences, 1934; 1934/216.S
      - Illinois, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 766)
  - Iowa, 1934; 1934/218
    - Iowa, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 766)
  - Kansas, 1934; 1934/219
    - Kansas, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 767)
  - Kentucky, 1934; 1934/220
    - Kentucky, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 768)
  - Louisiana, 1934; 1934/221
    - Louisiana, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 769)
    - Louisiana - Social Sciences, 1934; 1934/221.S
      - Louisiana, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 769)
  - Maine, 1934; 1934/222
    - Maine, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 769)
  - Maryland, 1934; 1934/223
    - Maryland, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 769)
  - Massachusetts, 1934; 1934/224
    - Massachusetts, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 769)
  - Minnesota, 1934; 1934/226
    - Minnesota, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 769)
  - Mississippi, 1934; 1934/227
    - Mississippi, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 770)
    - Mississippi - Reports, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 771)
    - Mississippi, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 772)
    - Mississippi - Nursing, 1934; 1934/227.C
      - Mississippi, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 772)
    - Mississippi - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/227.E
      - Mississippi, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 772)
  - Missouri, 1934; 1934/228
    - Missouri, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 772)
    - Missouri - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/228.E
  - Montana, 1934; 1934/229
    - Montana, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 773)
    - Montana, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 773)
    - Montana - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/229.E
      - Montana, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 773)
  - Nevada, 1934; 1934/231
    - Nevada, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 773)
  - New Mexico, 1934; 1934/234
    - New Mexico, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 773)
  - North Carolina, 1934; 1934/236
    - North Carolina - State Board of Health, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 774)
    - North Carolina - State Board of Health, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 775)
    - North Carolina - Milam, Frank, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 776)
    - North Carolina, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 777)
    - North Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/236.E
      - North Carolina, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 777)
  - North Dakota, 1934; 1934/237
    - North Dakota, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 777)
  - Ohio, 1934; 1934/238
    - Ohio, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 777)
  - Oregon, 1934; 1934/240
    - Oregon, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 778)
    - Oregon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/240.E
      - Oregon, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 778)
  - Pennsylvania, 1934; 1934/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 778)
    - Pennsylvania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1934; 1934/241.D
      - Pennsylvania, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 778)
    - Pennsylvania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/241.E
      - Pennsylvania, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 778)
  - Rhode Island, 1934; 1934/244
    - Rhode Island, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 778)
  - Samoa, 1934; 1934/245
    - Samoa, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 778)
  - South Carolina, 1934; 1934/246
    - South Carolina - State Board of Health, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 779)
    - South Carolina, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 780)
    - South Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/246.E
      - South Carolina, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 780)
  - South Dakota, 1934; 1934/247
    - South Dakota, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 780)
  - Tennessee, 1934; 1934/248
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 781)
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 782)
    - Tennessee, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 783)
    - Tennessee - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/248.E
      - Tennessee, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 783)
  - Texas, 1934; 1934/249
    - Texas, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 784)
    - Texas - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/249.E
      - Texas, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 784)
  - Utah, 1934; 1934/250
    - Utah, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 784)
    - Utah - Public Health Education, 1934; 1934/250.L
      - Utah, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 784)
  - Vermont, 1934; 1934/251
    - Vermont, 1934 (Box 99, Folder 784)
  - Virginia, 1934; 1934/252
    - Virginia, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 785)
    - Virginia - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 1934; 1934/252.Q
      - Virginia, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 785)
  - Washington, 1934; 1934/253
    - Washington, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 785)
  - West Virginia, 1934; 1934/254
    - West Virginia, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 786)
  - Wisconsin, 1934; 1934/255
    - Wisconsin, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 786)
    - Wisconsin - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/255.E
      - Wisconsin, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 786)
  - Wyoming, 1934; 1934/256
    - Wyoming, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 786)
  - Virgin Islands, 1934; 1934/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
    - Virgin Islands - Nursing, 1934; 1934/257.C
      - Virgin Islands, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
    - Virgin Islands - Malaria, 1934; 1934/257.I
      - Virgin Islands, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
  - South America, 1934; 1934/300
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/300.E
      - Central America, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
    - South America - Yellow Fever, 1934; 1934/300.O
      - Central America, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
  - Argentina, 1934; 1934/301
    - Argentina, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
    - Argentina - Yellow Fever, 1934; 1934/301.O
      - Argentina, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
  - Brazil, 1934; 1934/305
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1934; 1934/305.O
      - Brazil, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
      - KUM-2 Kumm, Henry W. "Seasonal Variations in Numbers of Mosquito Larvae Encountered in Test Containers in the State of Bahia, Brazil", 1934 (Box 558, Folder 3782)
      - SAW-5 Sawyer, W. H. "Trip of Inspection of Yellow Fever Activities, 1930-1934" (Box 558, Folder 3783)
  - Colombia, 1934; 1934/311
    - Colombia, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
    - Colombia - Nursing, 1934; 1934/311.C
      - Colombia, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/311.E
      - Colombia, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 787)
  - Costa Rica, 1934; 1934/313
    - Costa Rica, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 788)
    - Costa Rica - Public Health Demonstrations, 1934; 1934/313.J
      - Costa Rica, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 788)
    - Costa Rica - Health Services, 1934; 1934/313.K
      - Costa Rica, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 788)
    - Costa Rica - Public Health Education, 1934; 1934/313.L
      - Costa Rica, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 788)
  - Cuba, 1934; 1934/315
    - Cuba, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 788)
    - Cuba - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/315.E
      - Cuba, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 788)
  - Guatemala, 1934; 1934/319
    - Guatemala, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 788)
  - Mexico, 1934; 1934/323
    - Mexico - (A-C), 1934 (Box 100, Folder 789)
    - Mexico - Gunn, Selskar M., 1934 (Box 100, Folder 790)
    - Mexico - (H-Z), 1934 (Box 100, Folder 791)
    - GUNN-1 Gunn, Selskar M. Notes and Comments on a Visit to Mexico, September 2-November 15, 1934 (Box 558, Folder 3784)
    - Mexico - Public Health Demonstrations, 1934; 1934/323.J
      - Mexico, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 791)
  - Nicaragua, 1934; 1934/325
    - Nicaragua, 1934 (Box 100, Folder 791)
    - Nicaragua - Health Services, 1934; 1934/325.K
      - MAG-10 Magoon, E. H. "Report with Recommendation for Repair of the Intercepting Sewer of Managua", 1934 (Box 558, Folder 3785)
  - Panama, 1934; 1934/327
    - Panama, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 792)
    - Panama - Carley, Paul S., 1934 (Box 101, Folder 793)
    - Panama - Carley, Paul S., 1934 (Box 101, Folder 794)
    - Panama - Health - Listed Mail, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 795)
    - Panama - Milam, Frank, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 796)
    - Panama - Milam, Frank - St. Tomas Hospital, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 797)
    - Panama, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 798)
    - Panama, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 798)
    - MAG-9 Magoon, E. H. "Preliminary Report (and) ... summary of the Proposed Improvements ... for ... Panama Republic Towns...", 1934 (Box 559, Folder 3786)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/327.E
      - Panama, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 798)
    - Panama - Health Services, 1934; 1934/327.K
      - MAG-9 Magoon, E. H. "Preliminary Report (and) ... summary of the Proposed Improvements ... for ... Panama Republic Towns...", 1934 (Box 559, Folder 3786)
    - Panama - Public Health Education, 1934; 1934/327.L
      - Panama, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 798)
  - Paraguay, 1934; 1934/329
    - Paraguay, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 799)
  - Peru, 1934; 1934/331
    - Peru, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 799)
  - El Salvador, 1934; 1934/333
    - El Salvador, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 799)
    - El Salvador - Public Health Education, 1934; 1934/333.L
      - El Salvador, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 799)
  - Dominican Republic, 1934; 1934/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 799)
  - Venezuela, 1934; 1934/339
    - Venezuela, 1934 (Box 101, Folder 799)
  - Great Britain, 1934; 1934/400
    - Great Britain, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 800)
  - England, 1934; 1934/401
    - England - (A-M), 1934 (Box 102, Folder 800)
    - England - (N-Z), 1934 (Box 102, Folder 801)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1934; 1934/401.A
      - England, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 801)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1934; 1934/401.D
      - England, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 801)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/401.E
      - England, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 801)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1934; 1934/401.R
      - England, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 802)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1934; 1934/401.S
      - England, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 802)
  - Ireland, 1934; 1934/403
    - Ireland, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 803)
    - Ireland - Humanities and Arts, 1934; 1934/403.R
      - Ireland, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 803)
  - Scotland, 1934; 1934/405
    - Scotland, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 803)
  - Australia, 1934; 1934/410
    - Australia, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 803)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/410.E
      - Australia, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 803)
  - New South Wales, 1934; 1934/411
    - New South Wales, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 803)
  - New Zealand, 1934; 1934/418
    - New Zealand - Health - Watt, M. H., 1934 (Box 102, Folder 804)
    - New Zealand, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 805)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 805)
  - Fiji, 1934; 1934/419
    - Fiji, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 805)
  - Caribbean, 1934; 1934/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 806)
    - Caribbean Region, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 807)
    - Caribbean - Hookworm, 1934; 1934/420.H
      - Caribbean Region, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 807)
  - Marquesas Islands, 1934; 1934/422
    - Marquesa Islands, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 807)
  - Belize, 1934; 1934/425
    - British Honduras, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 807)
  - Canada, 1934; 02.1934/427
    - Canada, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 808)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1934; 1934/427.A
      - Canada, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 808)
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1934; 1934/427.D
      - Canada, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 808)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/427.E
      - Canada, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 808)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1934; 1934/427.L
      - Canada, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 808)
  - Jamaica, 1934; 1934/437
    - Jamaica - (A-M), 1934 (Box 103, Folder 809)
    - Jamaica - Saunders, G. M., 1934 (Box 103, Folder 810)
    - Jamaica - (S-V), 1934 (Box 103, Folder 811)
    - Jamaica - Washburn, B. E., 1934 (Box 103, Folder 812)
    - Jamaica - Washburn, B. E., 1934 (Box 103, Folder 813)
    - Jamaica - Washburn, B. E., 1934 (Box 103, Folder 814)
    - Jamaica, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 815)
    - Jamaica - Nursing, 1934; 1934/437.C
      - Jamaica, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 815)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 815)
    - Jamaica - Health Services, 1934; 1934/437.K
      - Jamaica, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 815)
    - Jamaica - Yellow Fever, 1934; 1934/437.O
      - Jamaica, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 815)
  - St. Lucia, 1934; 1934/457
    - St. Lucia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/457.E
      - St. Lucia, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 815)
    - St. Lucia - Malaria, 1934; 1934/457.I
      - St. Lucia, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 815)
  - India, 1934; 1934/464
    - India, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 816)
    - India - (Ch-Co), 1934 (Box 104, Folder 817)
    - India - Jacocks, W. P., 1934 (Box 104, Folder 818)
    - India - Jacocks, W. P., 1934 (Box 104, Folder 819)
    - India - (K-M), 1934 (Box 104, Folder 820)
    - India - (P-Z), 1934 (Box 104, Folder 821)
    - India - Nursing, 1934; 1934/464.C
      - India, 1934 (Box 105, Folder 822)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/464.E
      - India, 1934 (Box 105, Folder 822)
    - India - Declinations, 1934; 1934/464.F
      - India, 1934 (Box 105, Folder 822)
      - India, 1934 (Box 105, Folder 823)
    - India (Mysore), 1934; 1934/464.1
      - India - (Mysore), 1934 (Box 105, Folder 824)
      - India - (Mysore) - Sweet, W. C., 1934 (Box 106, Folder 825)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1934; 1934/466
    - Bengal, 1934 (Box 106, Folder 826)
  - United Provinces, 1934; 1934/467
    - United Provinces - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/467.E
      - Muktesarkumaun, 1934 (Box 106, Folder 826)
  - Africa, 1934; 1934/475
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1934; 1934/475.S
      - Africa, 1934 (Box 106, Folder 826)
  - North Africa Region, 1934; 1934/485
    - Egypt, 1934 (Box 106, Folder 826)
    - North Africa Region - Hookworm, 1934; 1934/485.H
      - COR-2 Cort, W. W. "Report on the Egyptian Project", 1934 (Box 559, Folder 3787)
    - North Africa Region - Yellow Fever, 1934; 1934/485.O
      - Egypt, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
  - South Africa, 1934; 1934/487
    - South Africa, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
  - France, 1934; 1934/500
    - France, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/500.E
      - France, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
    - France - Yellow Fever, 1934; 1934/500.O
      - France, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
    - France - Undulant Fever, 1934; 1934/500.P
      - France, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1934; 1934/500.R
      - France, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
  - Asia, 1934; 1934/600
    - Asia, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
    - Asia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 01934/600.E
      - Asia, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
    - Asia - Malaria, 1934; 1934/600.I
      - Asia, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 827)
  - China, 1934; 1934/601
    - China - Administration - (A-C), 1934 (Box 107, Folder 828)
    - China - Dyer, B. R. - Gee, N. Gist - Goodwill Commission to China, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 829)
    - China - (Gr-H), 1934 (Box 107, Folder 830)
    - China - (L-Z), 1934 (Box 107, Folder 831)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1934; 1934/601.A
      - China, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 831)
    - China - Nursing, 1934; 1934/601.C
      - China, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 831)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1934; 1934/601.D
      - China, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 831)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/601.E
      - China, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 832)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1934; 1934/601.R
      - China, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 832)
  - Japan, 1934; 1934/609
    - Japan, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 833)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1934; 1934/609.E
      - Japan, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 833)
    - Japan - Tuberculosis, 1934; 1934/609.T
      - Japan, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 833)
  - Thailand, 1934; 1934/617
    - Thailand, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 833)